Guide to the James Payne Alter Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Biographical Material, Series V
  - Furlough, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 665)
  - Furlough, Travel, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 666)
  - Furlough, Trip to California, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 667)
  - Furlough, Trip to Stony Point, NY, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 668)
  - Furlough, Trip to United Kingdom, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 669)
  - Study project, U.S.A., 1975 (Box 34, Folder 670)
  - United Presbyterian Church in U.S.A.: Missionary Salaries, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 671)
  - Study projects, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 672)
  - Travel diary, Korea and Japan (Box 34, Folder 673)
  - Travel diary, Pakistan trip, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 674)